# **Hina Naz**

# Data Analyst and Visualizer Web Developer

## **Contact Details**



0341-2639064



hina.hrm87@gmail.com



Yaseenabad, Karachi.

### **About Me**

Data Analyst with an ability to turn complex data into clear insights. Skilled in SQL, Python, Excel and Power Bi, I focus on identifying trends and supporting decision-making. Additionally, I have experience with the MERN stack, enabling me to integrate data analysis with web development.

https://github.com/hinanaz87

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/hina-naz/

f https://www.facebook.com/WordPressDesignsbyHina

#### Technical Skills

Python for DA HTML

SQL for DA CSS

Statistical Analysis Javascript Excel React Js

Power Bi WordPress

#### Soft Skills

- Team Work
- Problem Solving
- Self-Learning

# **Career Objective**

To join a dynamic and progressive organization offering ample opportunities of diversified exposure, where I can further polish my professional skills & knowledge.

# **Academic Qualification**

#### M.S in Public Administration

July 2011-June2012

(Course Work Done)

# **Professional Experience**

#### **The Speed Train**

Feb 2024 - Till date

Web Developer and Website Maintenance

#### **Duties and Responsibilities:**

Developing and maintaining websites

#### **Windoors Ventures**

May 2023 - Jun2024

Web Developer and Project Lead

#### **Duties and Responsibilities:**

Developing and maintaining websites Leading the Team

#### **Edvon Robotics**

March 2020- Jun2021

Stem Instructor and Content Developer

#### **Professional Certification**

#### **Certified Data Analyst**

Sep 2024- In Progress

(Karachi AI)

Data Analysis Using Python

#### **Mobile and Web Development**

Jan 2022- Jan 2023

(Saylani)

Web Development Course

#### WordPress

July 2022-Sep 2022

(Digital Institute of Pakistan) WordPress Mentorship Program

#### **Portfolio**

- Created Dashboards using Excel
- Data Analysis project using Python and SQL
- Created Portfolio Website (Using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JS)
   https://hinanaz87.github.io/Portfolio/
- Created Business Website (Using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JS) https://hinanaz87.github.io/Bootstrap-Single-Page-Website/
- Created E-Commerce Website (Using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JS) https://eccomerce-mg.netlify.app/